(Meemaw:)I appreciate your honesty, dear.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
And here's
some more honesty:
(Meemaw:)I don't like you very much.
(Amy:)Well, maybe I don't
like you either.
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Y-You have
to like each other.
Well, we have a 4:30 reservation
at Applebee's.
(Amy:)I think I should leave.
(Sheldon:)But why?
(Sheldon:)Other than
you two fighting,
(Sheldon:)we're having such a good time.
(Amy:)The minute you left the room,
your precious meemaw
(Amy:)started giving me
a really hard time.
(Amy:)I don't need this.
(Meemaw:)Let her go.
(Meemaw:)And under no circumstance
(Meemaw:)will you give her
that engagement ring.
(Amy:)What ring?
(Leonard:)Maybe we should give
them some privacy.
(Penny:)Yeah, yeah, yeah.
(Penny:)You go ahead.
I'll catch up with you.
(Sheldon:)You have
an engagement ring?
(Penny:)Yes.
(Amy:)Penny, did you know
about this?
(Penny:)All right, let's go.